{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_5_BZUR3S",
                "player_15_BZUR3S",
                "player_9_BZUR3S",
                "player_12_BZUR3S"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                5,
                15,
                9,
                12
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "pick_up",
                "stand",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -44780.054,
                    16229.031,
                    -22529.288,
                    0,
                    18.628421799504565,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -44909.273,
                    16151.128,
                    -22529.287,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -44743.144,
                    15341.321,
                    -22529.288,
                    0,
                    -44.8318344305942,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -44731.269,
                    16106.506,
                    -22523.427,
                    0,
                    124.6165436071056,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -45450.716,
            15307.028,
            -22522.707
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1340.1405000323452
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -44912.728,
            14962.451,
            -22522.577,
            0,
            83.01829449914753,
            0
        ],
        [
            -44917.397,
            16495.337,
            -22522.714,
            0,
            -76.78034239843173,
            0
        ],
        [
            -44445.61,
            15033.845,
            -22522.566,
            0,
            110.50943604429021,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_camo_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many men are depicted in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many humans are bald in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many humans are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many men in the scene are not bald?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many non-bald humans are in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. others"
                ],
                "answer": "A. lying down"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in the brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding an object",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. crouching",
                    "D. others"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding an object"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. lying down",
                    "C. holding an object",
                    "D. others"
                ],
                "answer": "A. standing"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouching",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. others"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouching"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. behind",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. behind"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. behind",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the left of"
            }
        }
    }
}